Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Pacific Telephone & Telegraph Company; See also: Telephones, 1958-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Page Mill Home Owners Association, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Page Mill Rd. Lots (Ramos & Thompson), 1961-1968 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Page, Ben M., 1945-1960 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Palo Alto Auto Sales Inc. - Used Cars, 1954-1962 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Palo Alto Bar Association, 1963-1965 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, 1974-1975 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Palo Alto City Charter, 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Palo Alto Clinic, 1971-1973 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Palo Alto Clinic, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Palo Alto Farm - Fences, 1934-1969 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 103 - Correspondence, 1945-1955 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 103 - Maps and Exhibits (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 105 - Correspondence, 1952-1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 105 - Exhibits (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 108, 1955-1969 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 72 (MacDonough) (Ormondale Ranch), 1931-1945 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 72 (MacDonough), 1950-1964 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 75 - Exhibits - Coldwell, Banker appraisal, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 75 - Litigation, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 75, 1955-1974 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 79, 1948-1964 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Palo Alto Farm - Lot 87 - Guernsey Field, 1952-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Palo Alto Hospital - Management Business, 1931-1953 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Palo Alto Times, 1958-1973 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Palo Alto, City of - Transportation, 1961-1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Palo Alto, City of - Agreement for water & gas, Junipero Serra Boulevard, 1957-1958 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Palo Alto, City of - Assessment District #11 for undergrounding of 60-kv line in the Stanford Industrial Park, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Palo Alto, City of - Assessment District for gas line, 1966-1969 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Palo Alto, City of - Athletic Center & Public Facilities, 1955-1966 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Palo Alto, City of - Comprehensive Plan - Exhibits, 1974-1976 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Palo Alto, City of - Comprehensive Plan 1/1974-8/1974, 2a (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Palo Alto, City of - Comprehensive Plan 9/1974-12/1974, 2b (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Palo Alto, City of - Comprehensive Plan to 12/1973, 1 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Palo Alto, City of - Council Meetings, 1956-1972 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Palo Alto, City of - Electrical Utilities (Overhead and Underground) - Exhibits, 1965-1967 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Palo Alto, City of - Financial Facts and Statistics, 1962-1977 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Palo Alto, City of - General Plan, 1961-1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Palo Alto, City of - General Plan, 1970-1973 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Palo Alto, City of - General Plans, 1955-1963 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Palo Alto, City of - Hoover Pavilion (old P. A. Hospital), 1, 1950-1958 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Palo Alto, City of - Hoover Pavilion (old P.A. Hospital), 1959-1973 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Palo Alto, City of - Mayfield Fire Station Industrial Park - Correspondence, 1954-1965 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Palo Alto, City of - Mayfield Fire Station Industrial Park - Lease File, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Palo Alto, City of - Radio Equipment, 1950-1955 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Palo Alto, City of - Sewers, 1930-1943 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Palo Alto, City of, 1933-1974 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- PAMTRANS, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 31)
- Pardoe, Russel, 1972-1979 (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Park, Charles F. Jr., 1946-1955 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Parking & Traffic - Exhibits (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Parking & Traffic - Foothill Crossing, 1959-1965 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Parking & Traffic #9, 1971-1977 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Parking & Traffic, 2, see: Pkg. & Trrf. Foothill Crossing, “Bicycles” and “Roads - Streets & Walks”, 1963-1965 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Parking & Traffic, 3, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Parking & Traffic, 4, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Parking & Traffic, 5, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Parking & Traffic, 6, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Parking & Traffic, 7, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Parking & Traffic, 8, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Parking Lot ÒBÓ- Panama St. Ext.- Via Ortega, 402B, 396H, 401F, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Parking Lots C & H, 402, 1964-1966 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Parking Structure Study, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Parks, George S., 1935-1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Paulsen, Jasper W., 1933-1952 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Payback Analysis for Insulating Old Pav. Ceiling, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Payroll - Personnel Project, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 29)
- Pearce Mitchell Project, 1971-1975 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Pease, Otis A., 1957-1966 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Pending Oil and Gas Matters, 1960-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Pending Oil and Gas Matters, 1960-1967 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Peninsula Community Hosp., 1944-1961 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Peninsula Housing Assoc., 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Peninsula Railway Co., 1921-1937 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Peninsula Railway, 1921-1934 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Peninsula Sanitary Service - Exhibits (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Peninsula Sanitary Service #2, 1968-1973 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Peninsula Sanitary Service 1962-1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Pereira, Joaquin (farm lease), 1958-1963 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Permits Refused, 1932-1962 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Personnel Office, 1970-1975 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Personnel Office, #1, 1955-1970 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Personnel Policies and Procedures - Stanford University Employees Association, 1968-1971 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Personnel Policies and Procedures - United Stanford Employees, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1957-1963 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1963-1970 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Pesch, Leroy H., 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Pesch, Leroy, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Peterson, Herbert E., 1945-1951 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Petroleum Engineering Building - Air Conditioning, 784, 1972-1975 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Petroleum Investments - Moorlane - Braden, 1962-1965 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- PH Chronological File, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Phase I, II, III Costs by Bldg., Mall, Parking, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Phi Delta Theta Fraternity, 1923-1939 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Phi Delta Theta, 1955-1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Phi Gamma Delta House Association, 1930-1939 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Phi Gamma Delta, 1938-1951 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Phi Kappa Psi, 1924-1945 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Phi Kappa Psi, 1938-1961 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Phi Kappa Sigma, 1935-1943 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Phi Kappa Sigma, 1938-1950 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Phi Kappa Sigma, 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Phi Sigma Kappa, 1938-1950 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Phi Sigma Kappa, 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Philbrick, Norman D., 1945-1956 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Photo-Mimeo Remodeling, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Photography - Mimeograph, 1941-1963 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Physical Plant - Nursery, 1940-1964 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Physical Plant - Proposed New Corp Yard, see also: Stan. Lin. Acc. Ctr. - Corp Yard, 1955-1960 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Physical Plant (formerly Buildings and Grounds Dept.), 1959-1962 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Physical Plant, 6/1/1962-8/31/1965 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Pine Hall Room 188-C Remodeling, (889), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 31)
- Pitman, Hayden W. (Tax Consultant) #1178, 1957-1971 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Placement Services, 1955-1972 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Planning Office #1, 1952-1972 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Plant Services - Bike Lock Company, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Plant Services - Contracts, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Plant Services - Exhibits (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Plant Services - Steam Plant, 1960-1970 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Plumbing, 1964-1965 (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Police Department - Police Training, 1962-1966 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Police Department, 1, see also: Parking & Traffic and “Security Problems”, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Police Department, 1965-1967 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Police Department, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Police Department, 2, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Police Department, 3, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Police Department, 4, 1971-1973 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Police Department, see also: Safety Office for previous correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Police Publicity, 1968-1971 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Polo Const. Loan Amort, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Polya Hall - Consolidation of CSD on the 2nd Floor, (897), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 29)
- Polya Hall - Relocation of the Center for Interdisciplinary Research, 899, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- Poole, Arthur B., 1938-1960 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Portola Valley Thoroughbred Training Center, #1, 1965-1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Portola Valley, Town of, Folder #1, 1955-1964 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Presentation to Palo Alto 10/30/1973 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- President’s Report, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- President’s Report, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Press - Assignments of Copyright, #1, 1956-1964 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Press - Budget, 1959-1970 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Press - Exhibits - Remodeling Drawings, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Press - General, 1951-1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Press - Wages, 1953-1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Press - Wages, 1964-1971 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Price, Miss Louise, 1937-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Price, Mrs. Marjorie B. (L.H.), 1934-1948 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Hospital - Planning, Engineering, Landscaping, 1954-1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Improvements (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Landscaping, 1957-1965 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Old Winery Building 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Professional - Administrative Area - Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Progress & Review SSC Renov. & Exp., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Project "M" - Background of Construction Figures, 1956-1959 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Project "M" - Contract AT(04-3)-363, Superseded by Contract AT(04-3)-400, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Project "M" - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- Project "M" - Proposal for Project "M", Review of Proposal, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Project "M"- 363 Contract Drafts, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Project "M" (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Project "M" - ABA Subcontract (S-128) - Documents and Drafts, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Project "M" - ABA Subcontract (S-128) - Documents and Drafts, 1961-1963 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Project "M" - ABA Subcontract (S-128) - Schedules, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Project "M" - Subcontracts (Other than Aetron - Blume - Atkinson, S-128), 1960-1964 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Project "M"- ABA Subcontract (S-128) - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Proposed Construction Management Control System Prepared for Stanford University Office of Facilities and Properties (Binder) (Box 35)
- Proposed Roads - San Mateo County, Santa Clara County, 1950-1952 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Psychiatry Clinic Bldg. - Change Orders, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 29)
- Psychiatry Clinic Bldg. - Disbursements, 587, 1971-1974 (Box 115, Folder 27)
- Psychiatry Clinic Bldg. - Legal, 587, 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 28)
- Psychiatry Clinic Building - Correspondence, P.O. #587, 1970-1973 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Psychiatry Clinic Building - Inspector’s Report & Supplements, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Psychiatry Clinic Building - Stage II, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Purchasing - Claim against Linford Air and Refrigeration Co., 1965 (Box 70, Folder 32)
- Purchasing - Policies and Procedures, 1965-1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Purchasing - Stores Relocation, 1970-1972 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Purchasing - Stores Relocation, 1, 1961-1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Purchasing - Stores Relocation, 2, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Purchasing and Stores Relocation - Legal, 383, 1964-1966 (Box 102, Folder 21)
- Purchasing Department, 2, 1959-1961 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Purchasing Department, 3, 1961-1963 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Purchasing Department, 6, 1966-1969 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Purchasing Department, 7, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Purchasing Department, 8, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Purchasing Department, 9, 1971-1974 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Purissima Hills County Water District, 1952-1965 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Quad Renovation, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Quad VII Electrical Lines - Legal Documents, 348, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Quad VII Steam Lines - Legal Documents, 347, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Quad, 1933-1955 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Quarry - General (Agmt. with S.M. County), 1951-1965 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Quarry - Sondgroth proposal and others, 1956-1964 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Quarry - Utah Construction Co. - Rehabilitation, 1953-1959 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Questionnaires, 1946-1972 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- R & D Bldg., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Raab, George R., 1934-1950 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Radiation Therapy - Contract Changes, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Radiation Therapy - Correspondence, File No. 1, 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Radiation Therapy - Correspondence, File No. 2, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Radiation Therapy - Correspondence, File No. 3, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Radiation Therapy - Disbursements, 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Radiation Therapy - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Radiation Therapy - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Radiation Therapy - Lab Testing Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Radiation Therapy - Legal, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Radio Station KZSU, 1966-1971 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Ramsey, Mrs. A. C. (See Espinosa, Jr.), 1952-1953 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Real Estate - 2209 Laguna St., San Francisco County, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Real Estate - Butte County (Doyle), 1919 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- Real Estate - Campus - 663 San Juan (Solon Shedd Residence), 1939 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Real Estate - Campus - 666 Mayfield (formerly R. L. Templeton residence), 1940 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Real Estate - County of Alameda, City of Alameda, 1929-1936 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Real Estate - Deeds, 1873-1937 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Real Estate - Denver Property, 1936 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Real Estate - Forms - Deeds, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Real Estate - Los Gatos, CA - Mortimer C. Leventritt property, 1940 (Berton Crandall photographs) (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Real Estate - Palo Alto Farm Lands - Leased and Unleased, 1932-1941 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Real Estate - Rental & Sale Record, San Francisco (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Real Estate - Tehama County - Vina Ranch, 1935 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Real Estate Purchases - San Francisco, 1928-1931 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Real Estate, 1970-1974 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Red Barn Relocation, 782, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Red Cross Disaster Relief, 1947-1953 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Red Cross, 1930 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Redetzke, E.W., 1945-1955 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Registration - Pre-Registration, 1941-1956 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Reid, George, 1953-1955 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Reinhart, Kury F., 1933-1960 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Renovations - Houses for Academic Use, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Rent Survey - University-owned Property, 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Report - Water Sources for Stanford University (includes evaluation of Corps of Engineers flood control project), 1959 (Box 58)
- Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Reprographic Services (formerly Photo-Repro), 1966-1971 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Reprographic Services (formerly Photo-Repro), 1, 1963-1966 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Request for Check, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Requisitions - 7 SAA 001 94610, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Requisitions - 7 SAZ 001 only - Business Office, 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Requisitions - Business Office, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Requisitions - Business Office, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Requisitions - Business Office, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Requisitions - Expense Reports, 1961-1965 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Requisitions - Expense Reports, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Requisitions - General, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Requisitions - General, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Requisitions - General, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Requisitions - General, 1968-1972 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Requisitions - Work Orders, 1969-1974 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Requisitions, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Requisitions, 7 SAZ 001 only - Business Office, 1969-1973 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Research - Equipment Accountability, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Research & Development - Budget and Fiscal, 1969-1975 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Research & Development - Bulletins, Field Orders (P.O. 512), 1971-1973 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Research & Development - Correspondence No. 1 (P.O. 512), 1969-1971 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Research & Development - Correspondence No. 2 (P.O. 512), 1971 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Research & Development - Correspondence No. 3 (P.O. 512), 1972 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Research & Development - Correspondence No. 4 (P.O. 512), 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Research & Development - Correspondence No. 5 (P.O. 512), 1973-1975 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Research & Development - Employee Interviews, 1971-1972 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Research & Development - Exhibits, 1969-1972 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Research & Development - Health, Education & Welfare - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Research & Development - Job Meetings - Addit. Instrruct., 1971-1972 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Research & Development - Progress Pictures, 1971-1972 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Research & Development - Unsuccessful bids, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Research & Development (Education) - Disbursements File No. 2 (512), 1972-1976 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Research & Development Center - Contract Changes (P.O. 512), 1971-1972 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Research & Development Center - Disbursements File No. 1 (P.O. 512), 1969-1972 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Research & Development Center - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports #2, #512, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Research & Development Center - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, #512, 1971-1973 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Research & Development Center - Lab Testing Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Research & Development Center - Legal (512), 1969-1972 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Research and Development - Carpeting Deficiencies, 1972-1974 (Box 109, Folder 30)
- Research and Development - Legal, 1969-1974 (Box 109, Folder 31)
- Research Sites, Folder I, 1950-1963 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Research Sites, Folder II, 1963-1969 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Research, 1961-1970 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Residences - Analysis of Apr. 6, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Residences - Branner, 1944-1962 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Residences - Crothers, Folder 2, 1953-1956 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Residences - Custodial Service, 1960-1965 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Residences - Director of, 1, 1950-1960 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Residences - General, 1955-1960 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Residences - General, 1961-1965 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Residences - Graduate School of Business, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Residences - Jacks, David & Margaret - Programming, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Residences - Loan Support and Comparative Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Residences - Moore, Robert S. 1 - Programming, 1960-1962 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Residences - Moore, Robert S. 2 - Programming, 1963-1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Residences - Planning, 1951-1962 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Residences - Toyon, 1947-1961 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Residences - Union, 1964-1966 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Residences - Wilbur - Faculty Master’s Residence, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Residences - Wilbur, 1954-1964 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Residences and Food Service - Renovation, Summer 1965 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Residential Area - Correspondence on Other Developments, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Responses to Chapter One of Commission Report, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Rest Home - Men's, 1946-1966 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Rest Home - Women's, 1953-1966 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Reynolds, Prof. Charles N. and Pansy, 1934-1954 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Richardson, Inez G. (Mrs.), 1942-1957 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Richman, Frederick I. Trust, 1974-1975 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Riding Ring - Construction, 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Riding School (3), 1954-1964 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Roads - Arboretum Road, 1955-1963 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Roads - California Avenue, 1954-1955 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Roads - Campus Drive - Landscaping - Bahr & Ledoyen, Construction Contract 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Roads - Campus Drive (Plans for complete road), for specific sections, see other files, 1956-1964 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Roads - El Camino Real Widening - Exhibits (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Roads - El Camino Real Widening - Legal, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Roads - El Camino Real Widening - Matadero Creek South, 1964-1967 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Roads - El Camino Real Widening - University Avenue to Matadero Creek, File 1, 1958-1961 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Roads - El Camino Real Widening - University Avenue to Matadero Creek, File 2, 1961-1966 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Roads - Escondido Improvements - Construction, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Roads - Escondido Improvements - Exhibits, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Roads - Escondido Improvements, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Roads - Foothill Expressway - Phase II, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Roads - Foothill Expressway and Arastradero Rd. Widening - Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Roads - Foothill Expressway and Arastradero Road Widening - Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Roads - Galvez - Embarcadero Road Intersection and Realignment, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Appraisals & Correspondence with General Counsel, Confidential, 1963-1967 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Charts and Reports, 1960-1967 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Community relations, 1957-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Condemnation Actions #2, 1967-1974 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Condemnation Actions, Board Actions, 1956-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Construction, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Departmental & Tenant Installations, 1957-1967 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Miscellaneous, 1955-1973 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Page Mill Road Interchange, Condemnation, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - SLAC Crossing (see Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Freeway Crossing - Right of Entry) (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Slide Exhibits, 1963-1967 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Slide, 1964-1970 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway - Test Borings, 1960-1967 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Roads - Junipero Serra Freeway -Crossings for Roads & Utilities, 1962-1969 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Roads - LM:5 Area (See Industrial Area - LM:5 Roads & Utilities) (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Roads - Page Mill Road -1965 - Exhibits from Foothill Exp. to Junipero Serra Freeway, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Roads - Peripheral, 1948-1957 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Roads - Portola Road - Widening of, 1952-1954 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Roads - Sand Hill Road - #2, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Roads - Sand Hill Road - Exhibits, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Roads - Sand Hill Road - Folder #1, 1950-1966 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Roads - Sand Hill Road #3, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Roads - Stanford Avenue - Abandonment (Box 65, Folder 16)